众所周知  外科医生并不和蔼
Surgeons aren't known for being warm and cuddly
他们傲慢  不耐烦  尖酸刻薄
They are arrogant, impatient, mean as often as nugget
你可以尝试化疗配合免疫疗法
You can go with straight up chemo and immunol therapy
成功几率不高  不过
The survival rates are prttey low, but
有很多成功的亚态切除病例
There is a lot of succsefull metastat-sectomies.
也许可以切除掉它
We could propbly just, you know, cut this thing out
人们认为他们不会有朋友
You think they wouldn't have friends
-因为没人能受得了他们  -藏什么呢
- 'cuz who could stand them. - What are you hiding?
没什么  工作上的东西
Nothing. its just work stuff.
-是什么  手术  -不是  没什么
- What is that? physical surgery?  - No. its nothing.
没什么
Its nothing
无所谓了  他们选了我
Whatever it is, they're gonna pick me
选我做主刀手术  全因我的良好表现
I'm already for the solo. Just for training well.
-你确定不告诉他吗  -我确定
- Are you sure you just won't tell him  - Yes, I am sure
好吧  听着  我找了一大堆资料
OK look, I researched a ton of information here
在见这位肿瘤学家之前  全部看完
You should read all of this before you see this oncologist.
这是什么
What is that?
我找了戈尔丁医生  他给我联系了斯汪特
I called Dr. golding and he gave me a direct profile of Dr. Swender.
我尽量安排你今天见他
So I gonna try and get you in today
-你们干嘛呢  -我说了我没事
-What are you doing here  -I told you I was fine
你太有问题了
Oh, god. You are so not fine.
只要知道德里克没事   我就没事
I will be fine if i knew Derek is fine
怎么  你还没他的消息吗
What? You still haven't heared from him? No word?
伊兹  你今天不打算请病假吗
Izzie, don't you think you should call in sick today?
-为什么  -要看的材料太多
- What? Why? - Because this is a lot of reading
而且你有病在身
and you are sick
-你们走吗  今天有个大手术  -走
- You guys coming? Big surgery today  - Yeah
伊兹  你
Izzie, just
但医生就像是重感冒
but surgeons are like a bad cold
讨人厌  却又顽固
nasty but persistent
-主任  我问你件事  -斯隆
- Chief, I need to ask you about  - Sloan
有德里克的消息吗
Have you heared from Derek
没有
No.
不好意思  你刚才说
Oh, I am sorry. You were saying?
-梅瑞狄斯  -我没他的消息
- Meredith - no, i don't know how he is.i have heared nothing
今天没有  昨天没有  前天也没有
Nothing today, nothing yesterday, nothing the day before that.
我也不会再去找他了
and no I will not go back out there.
为什么把我的手术换时间了
hey, why move my surgery.
-主任  主任  -别叫了
- Chief, Chief.  - Don't. Just don't
他现在急躁得很  在我们面前全然失控
he's a wreck.He's disintegrating before our very eyes.
所以男人比女人死得早
That's why men die earlier than women.
-手术安排一团糟  -他不能没有谢博德
- board's a mess.  - he can't lose sheperd
我想去劝他回来
i'll go talk a sense to him, but
-但我事太多了  -你给他打过电话吗
- just got too much on my plate  - have you tried calling him?
无数遍了
about a hundred times
不会吧  你想让我去森林找他
no. oh. you want me to go to the woods. no .
我才不进森林  那么脏  虫子又多
I don't do woods. the woods are dirty and there are many many bugs
我该跟他怎么说啊  跟他又不熟
What am I gonna say to the guy? I barely know him.
不用跟他很熟  你们都是外科医生
You don't have to know him. You're both surgeons.
又都奋斗在同一战线
and you've been to the same war
只要提醒他  我们都经历过失败
Just remind him we've all been there.
但我们都回来了
We all came back.
你这可是恐吓  知道吗
You are kind of a bully, you know that?
没用我就不这么干了
Wouldn't do it if it didn't work so well.
这是你们见过最大的手术
This is one of the biggest surgeries
绝无仅有  一定要用心
You may have ever get anywhere near. So please pay attention
病人38岁  男性
The patient is 38 year old man
12年前被人醉酒驾车撞倒
Who is hit by a drunk driver 12 years ago.
面部受到严重损伤
He suffered severe facial trouble
他没有鼻子  没有嘴唇
He's got no nose no lips
所以我们称他为通气口
Thats why we dubed him blowhole
曾做过9次修复重建手术
He's had 9 reconstructive surgeries
都没能修复全部面容及官能
None of which brought back full form or function
这样的手术全世界做过4例
This surgery have already been done 4 times worldwide and
病人都必须经过严格的心理测试
All of the candidates have to undergo extensive psychologicl testing
以决定他们是否能够承受
to determine wheather or not they can handle the process
心理测试的原因在于
psychological components are assigned cuz
术后有很可能发生排斥或是感染
this surgery has a huge chance of rejection or infection
病人会被安置在抗菌房间内
patient will have to be in a room ...
我们负责抗排斥用药
We will be on right for antirejection drugs
潜在危险包括肺癌  糖尿病
Which pretty might risk for lung foma, diabetes,
高血压
Hypertension, Remon Failure
我听他们叫他"通气口"
I hear they call the dude blowhole
你说什么
What did you just say?
没什么  只是听见一个外号而已
Nothing I just heared the other nickname.
以后不许再这么说
Don't talk anymore, ever!
额滴神呀
Holly crap!
-通气口真贴切  -我说什么来着
- Blowhole is right  - What did i tell you?
医生讨人厌  攻击性强  死不回头
Surgeons, nasty, aggressive, unstoppable.
但你会需要这样的人帮忙
just the kind of people you want on your side
尤其是你倒霉的时候
when you are really screwed
女士们  先生们  这位是戴维·杨先生
Ladies and gentlemen this is Mr David Young
今天他将接受面部移植手术
Today he will be receiving a face transplant
亨特医生和他的团队
Dr. Hunt and his team
将用捐献者的皮肤进行面部移植
Will be recovering the donor facial graft.
我们要修复杨先生面部70%的皮肤
We're replacing 70% of mr. Young's face.
-可以在这里看到残缺部分  -看这儿也行
- see the deficit here. - or here.
捐献修复包括他的鼻子
The donor recovery will include his nose
左眼  嘴唇  左颧骨
Left eye, lips, left zygoma.
为什么异体移植术
Why will allotransplantation
比传统技术效果好
Work better than traditional techniques?
外观修补更完善
Better aesthetic outcome,
有利于面部神经再分布
Which allows for reinnervation of the facial nerves,
改善机能效果
Giving a better functional result.
很好  格蕾医生
Very good, Dr. Grey.
回到杨先生的面部问题
Then we'll position the flap over Mr. Young's face.
如何分辨移植成功与否
How do we know when we're in the clear?
皮肤变粉色
When the graft turns pink.
非常好
Excellent.
戴夫  还有问题要问吗
Dave, any questions for us?
有没有人见过捐献者
H-has anyone seen the donor?
他的年龄  肤色  血型和你完全一致
Yes. he's a match with your age, skin tone and blood type.
他长什么样
What does he look like?
你会满意的
I think you'll be satisfied.
我开玩笑的  是张脸就行了
Who am I kidding? it's a face, right?
只要手术后不再是被人指指点点的怪物
If I end up anything above a point-and-stare freak,
对我来说  就是成功的手术
I'm gonna call it a success.
克莱夫  你跟我做捐赠者手术
Karev, you're with me on the donor.
一般我们是即时取样的
Usually we take them at the same time,
但捐赠者生命维持不了多久  抓紧时间吧
But the donor's life support is fading fast. we gotta move.
-谢谢您  -斯蒂文斯  格蕾
- Oh, thank you, sir. - uh, Stevens, Grey.
在
Yes!
不是你  另外一个格蕾
No, the other Grey.
-是吗  好  -好
- Really? uh, great. - great.
你刚才表现非常好
You did an awesome job in there.
术前化验结果出来后  来找我
Why don't you call me after the pre-op labs come in?
斯隆医生  只需要一个住院医生吗
Dr. Sloan, only one resident?
等贝利来吧  这人已经够多了
Wait for Bailey. there's already going to be enough of a crowd.
搞什么
What the hell?
伊兹
Uh, Izzie,
你没时间跟斯隆做手术了
I don't think you have time to scrub in with Sloan.
-别操心  我能应付的了  -"非常出色"
- Don't worry about it. I can handle it. - awesome job.
估计昨晚上床时泄露过考题了
She probably quizzed him in bed last night.
她能参与"通气口"的手术  因为她跟斯隆
She gets to work on blowhole because she gave Sloan a--
给我闭嘴
Shut your mouths!
把病例填完  我等会儿回来
Finish the chart. I'll be back.
欧麦利  格蕾
Uh, o'malley, Grey,
你俩负责术前和术后工作
I need you on pre-ops and post-ops.
但今天有场很重要的手术
But there's the biggest surgery in the world happening here today.
是啊  一半的主治医生都要参加
Yes, and half our attendings are involved,
所以才需要能干的住院医生
which is why we need strong residents on pre-ops and post-ops.
样你今天跟我一起
Yang, you're with me today.
是你粉墨登场的时候了  什么
You're moving to the big leagues. what?
-她做主刀手术  -今天吗
- She gets a solo? - today?
一位患疝气的老年妇女  交给你了
A nice old lady with a hernia. you're gonna fix it.
恭喜
congratulations.
我知道我该再热情一点儿
I know I should seem more enthusiastic,
但我实在没那么伟大
But I'm not that big a person.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
心怀邪念有错吗
Is it wrong to have hatred in your heart?
早上好  苏利女士  我是克里斯蒂娜·杨医生
Good morning, ms. sully. I'm Dr. cristina yang.
今天由我为你做疝修复术
I'll be performing your hernia repair today.
幸会
Lovely to meet you.
开始之前你什么问题要问吗
do you have any questions before we get started?
有啊  能帮我把钱包拿来吗
Oh, yes. can you hand me my purse, please?
我朋友要我问一大堆问题
My friends gave me a bunch of questions,
我也记不住
And, well, I can't remember any of them, of course.
他们这么担心我
They're such worrywarts.
他们都去欧洲旅行了
They're all off on a european tour without me.
当他们知道疝气病情时  都说不去了
They threatened not to go when this hernia
但是我说不行
Started becoming a problem, but I told them no, no.
这次旅游我们已经计划了2年了
We have been saving up for this for two years.
只要有医生证明
It helped that I was able to get my deposit back
我就可以把保证金拿回来
With a doctor's note. mm-hmm.
克里斯蒂娜·杨
Cristina Yang.
对
Yes.
不行  必须是今天
No, no, it has to be today.
已经到第四阶段了
It's stage iv.
不行  她必须见斯汪特医生
No, she has to see Dr. swender,
不是搭档
Not--not a partner.
抱歉  夫人
Uh... um, I'm sorry, ma'am.
等我稍后回来给你做细查时
Um, I will get to your questions
再回答你的问题  好吗
When I come back to examine you, okay?
推荐人是戈尔丁
Referral was golding. golding.
现在喝酒太早了吧
It's a little early in the day for that,
不觉得吗
Don't you think?
你好像我老妈一样
You sound like my mother.
我见过你妈妈  挺喜欢她的
Uh, I met your mother. I liked her.
谁叫你来的  理查德
Who sent you--richard?
贝利
Uh, Bailey.
对啊
Of course.
我很遗憾你的病人死了
Look, I'm sorry about your patient.
我知道打击很大
I know how hard it could be.
几年前我有过一个病人
I-i had a patient a couple of years ago--
还不算老  大概50岁
Uh, Young guy, 50 maybe.
简单的膝关节置换手术
Simple knee replacement.
术后情况很好
He was post-op, he was fine.
我甚至让他妻子给他带午饭吃
I even told his wife she could go and get him lunch.
这个手术太简单了  根本不算什么
I mean, it was a simple knee replacement. it was nothing.
但是他开始喘不上气
But, uh, he'd been getting short of breath,
所以我加了术后肺栓塞血液稀释
So I put him on blood thinners for a post-surgical p.e.
后来他开始吐暗红色的血
And, uh, it wasn't until he was vomiting up dark red blood,
他看着我  眼神好像在说他要死了
Looking me in the eye telling me that he was dying
我才意识到自己做错了
That I figured it out-- that I was wrong.
并不是肺栓塞  而是内出血
That it wasn't a p.e. he was bleeding internally.
本来不会致命的  但由于血液稀释
And it wouldn't have been fatal, but the blood thinners...
上帝  我永远忘不了他妻子的表情
God, I will never forget the look on his wife's face...
当她拿着三明治回来
When she came back with that sandwich in her hand,
问我为什么他丈夫不在房间里
Asking me why her husband wasn't in his room anymore.
你怎么办
How do you live with it?
是你杀了他
Killing him...
把他从妻子身边带走
Taking him from his wife--
你怎么办
How do you live with it?
这叫做医疗事故  叫做失误
We call it malpractice. we call it a mistake.
我知道这种叫法
Yeah, I know what we call it.
我在问你  当你早上睁开眼
I'm asking you, when you get up in the morning,
如何面对镜子里的自己
How do you look at yourself in the mirror?
我是
I'm not--i'm--i'm...
我是在问你
I'm asking.
我能喝点儿吗
Can I get one of those?
是因为不知道才难受
It's the not knowing that does it--
不知道他怎么样  回没回来
Not knowing if he's okay, not knowing if he's coming back.
可能我被甩了
Maybe I've just been dumped.
我都不知道自己是不是单身
I mean, it's not knowing if I'm single
一整天把我搞的想吐
That makes me want to throw up all day long.
-你根本没听我说  是吧  -对不起
- You are not listening to me, are you? - uh, sorry.
不  没事儿  我理解
No, no, that's okay. I get it.
我有了主刀手术  还有个兵哥哥
You've got the solo surgery and g.i. joe.
日子多美好啊  没空理我了
It's a charmed life. you don't have time for me.
我可没有兵哥哥  就是亲了几次而已
I have not had g.i. joe. we've kissed a couple times.
就像普通朋友那样
It's like friends with benefits,
没有什么
Without the benefits.
还没做吗
Still no sex?
说了日子一点也不美好
Mnh-mnh. not a charmed life.
脾脏切除术的化验结果
Lab results on the splenectomy.
要不要问
Do we ask?
不用  他会说的
No... 'cause he might tell us.
你能想像得到吗
Can you imagine?
这家伙有家人  对吧
This guy's got a family, right?
老婆  孩子
A wife, kids?
有一天他们在街上散步
One day they're gonna be walking down the street
看见他的脸贴在别人身上
And see his face on somebody else's body.
好恐怖啊
It's kinda creepy, right?
杨先生不会跟捐献者一摸一样
Mr. Young won't look exactly like the donor.
没有哪两个人的基本面部结构
The underlying facial structure
是完全一样的
Of any two people can be very different.
再说人的特征远不止皮肤  骨骼
plus, a person's identity is more than just skin and bone--
还包括表情  风格  眼神
His expressions, his style, his eyes.
捐赠者的家属认不出这张脸的
The donor's family wouldn't recognize this face on anyone else.
移植手术的医生们等不及了
Transplant surgeons are getting antsy.
移植手术的医生总是等不及
Transplant surgeons are always antsy.
要把活体组织放进冰柜
They can't relax until they've got live tissue in their coolers.
好了  我要开始最后的分离操作了
All right, I am making the final dissection.
克莱夫  从太阳穴那里夹住
Karev, take a hold right at the temple
慢慢提起来
And gently...lift
别把皮肉撕破了
Don't tear the flesh.
太帅了
Awesome.
切口的柔软度良好
Tenderness around the incision is normal.
没有感染的迹象  重新处理一下伤口
No signs of infection. Would you redress that wound?
梅根  你去一下二十...
Uh, Megan, will you please go to 20...
去一下22-14房
Go to room 22-14 and...
谢谢
Thanks.
去把引流管取下来  没事了再去吧
Just take out the drain... When you're ready?
我要问你个私人问题
Uh, I know it seems personal,
若非必须  我们也不会问
And we wouldn't ask if we didn't need to know,
你放过屁了吗
But have you passed gas yet?
抱歉
Sorry.
确认之后才能让你出院
We can't release you until that happens--
-放过了吗  -不好意思  我是想听
- The gas. - I'm sorry. I'm trying to listen.
但他们怎么是这个样子
But are they supposed to look like that?
什么样子
Like what?
一个手流血  一个眼圈打肿
The bleeding and the shiner,
还有那个貌似有自杀倾向
And that one looks like she's suicidal.
他们真的是医生
They're supposed to be doctors?
目前我们对此暂不表态
We're gonna reserve judgment on that for right now.
一群怪胎
Freak show.
我们到底拿他们怎么办
What the heck do we do with them?
把他们锁到柜子里去行不
can we shove them in a locker?
跟他们谈谈好了
I guess we should just talk to them.
不要  我们是专业人士
No. We're professionals,
他们这明显是私事
and that's clearly personal.
况且还会浪费我们的时间
besides, we'll just waste time.
就看不到主刀手术及脸部移植术了
We'll never get to see the solo surgery or the face transplant.
对  这点说得真对
Oh, that's a-- yeah, that's a good point.
那我们  我们就当没看见吧
I guess, well, we should-- we should just ignore it then.
对  当没看见好了
yeah, we should just ignore it.
这才是专业的做法
It's the professional thing to do.
没错  专业地当没看见
yeah, professionally ignore them.
你得接受所有这些药物治疗
It's important that you take all the medications,
否则可能会发生
Uh, because there's a risk of--
排斥反应和感染  我知道
Risk of rejection and infection. I know.
你已经给我灌输了几万次了
I know. you drilled it into my head a thousand times.
你的家人来了吗  因为
And is your family here yet? I'm--i just ask because
你手术后得需要有人来照顾你
Someone's gonna need to take care of you afterwards.
我没有家人
I don't have family,
但手术后会有些朋友来看我的
But my friends are coming after the surgery.
我很期待见他们  给他们看我的新样子
I'm excited to meet them and show them my new face.
我们在兰花爱好者聊吧里相识
We met in an online chat room for orchid lovers,
当然  我们并未真正见过
And, well, um, we've never actually "met" met, so...
戴夫  手术后
Dave, um, after the surgery,
此设备会帮助你锻炼用来呼吸的肌肉
This device is gonna help prevent lung problems
以防止肺部问题出现
By exercising the muscles you use to breathe.
-起来练习一下  好吗  -坐直
- I'd like you to practice on it now, okay? - Sit up straight.
轻轻吸气三次  然后把气吐进
Take three easy breaths and then blow... into that...
洞里
Hole.
够了
That's it.
你们两个都跟我出去
Both of you in the hall, now.
你们完全没觉得不妥吗
You really think that was okay?!
你们哪里像个医生
You think that was doctorly?!
你们俩去做其他事
you two find something else to do.
你究竟怎么回事儿
What the hell is going on with you?
他们俩开犯忌的玩笑
They were making completely inappropriate jokes
完全不顾病人的感受
At the expense of the patient right in front of him.
我一直在努力教他们
I have been trying to teach them,
他们这么无情  太不像话了
And they were cruel and inappropriate.
好了  他们是不像话
okay, they were inappropriate.
你知道还有什么不像话吗  就是你
You know what else is inappropriate? this. you.
我很宝贝这个病例
This case is my baby.
我花了三年的时间来准备
I've spent three years planning for it,
我不会允许你还有你的情绪
And you and your emotional life
来搞砸我的病例
Are not about to piss all over it.
-这个病例你别参加了  -不行
- You're off the case.  - No.
他需要我守着他
he needs me in there with him.
你不能把他丢给那群实习生
You can't leave him alone with those interns.
你想呆在里面照顾他的感情  随你
Okay, fine. you want to be there for his feelings?
只准在手术前后才可以
You can be there before and after the surgery.
你不准进我的手术室
But you're not coming in my O.R.
斯蒂文斯  不管你在搞些什么
And whatever's going on with you, Stevens,
你得好好控制你的情绪
You better get it under control.
我找到了
I found them.
什么  关于手术的问题
What? oh, um, the, uh, questions about the surgery?
有个一起旅游的朋友  比尔·费格森
One of my friends who went on the trip--Bill Ferguson.
他退休前是外科医生
He's a retired surgeon,
他让我问你这些问题
and he told me to ask you these,
但我找不着眼镜了
But I can't seem to find my glasses.
真该叫些朋友来
My friends should be here.
我总是随处放眼镜
I'm always putting my glasses down somewhere,
-他们总能帮我找着  -好了
- And they always find them for me-- - okay,
你是否还能去接送孙子
"will you finally be able to pick up your grandkids?"
这  这真是医生写的问题吗
Is--is this a question from a doctor?
不是  我其他朋友也帮我想了些问题
No. no, my other friends helped me with some questions,
我还自己加了一些  比如  会疼吗
Plus I added a few on my own, like will it hurt?
会疼吗
Will it... hurt?
会给你麻醉的
You'll be anesthetized.
我知道
Oh, yes, I know that.
我是说  麻醉过后会疼吗
I mean, after, will it hurt?
应该会有正常的术后疼痛
Uh, you should expect normal, post-operative pain.
什么事
Yes.
对
不是吧  太棒了
Oh, no. that is fantastic.
我接受  我接受
No, I'll--i'll take it. I'll take it.
太感谢了  谢谢
Thank you so much. thank you.
我会马上跟她联系的
No, I'll get in touch with her right away.
两点半  任何时间都行
Um, 2:30? anytime is fine.
我已经检查了22-13  19和33号病房
So I've covered 22-13, 19 and 33.
好的  我查了20-11和20-07病房
Yeah, okay. and I've got 20-11 and 20-07.
小梅  伊兹不大对劲
Mer, there is something wrong with Izzie.
你指什么
Uh, what do you mean?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我只知道有些事不大对劲
All I know is that there is something wrong.
你知道的  乔治
Well, you know, george,
实习生已经让我们烦透了
We're already drowning in intern drama.
不能再跟住院医生瞎掺合
We don't need resident drama, too.
如果真的有事  她会告诉我们的
If it's a problem, she'll tell us.
那之前  就别管了
Until then, just ignore it.
再说一次  别管了
I repeat, ignore it.
我的天  到底怎么了
What in god's name is going on?
只是私人问题
it's a personal issue,
我们想给他们一些个人空间
And we are just trying to give them their privacy.
你们难道认为
Oh, do you think for a second
我愿意掺合你们当初实习时的烂事
I wanted to get involved with your little intern dramas?
-我们没那么坏  -在拉斯维加斯结婚
- We were not this bad. - oh, uh, getting married in vegas,
跟主治医生乱搞  剪断心室辅助装置的线
Shaking up with attendings, cutting l-vad wires?
听着  你们没必要喜欢
Look, you don't have to like it,
但你们必须处理这些事
but you have to manage it.
我们已经控制住情况了
Oh, we've got it under control.
别走  我爱你  梅根
Wait! I love you, Megan!
先生  你没事吧
Sir. Are you ok?
真是抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不管你们俩怎么回事儿
Whatever it is the two of you have going on,
现在起别闹了
it stops now.
-我没有  -她说话时你们最好别插嘴
- I didn't  - I-i don't think you should talk while she's talking.
你们吓到了病人
You are scaring the patients.
你们令医院蒙羞
And you're making this hospital look ridiculous,
也让我们显得很差劲
And you're making us look incompetent.
-我们已经  -别说了
- No, but we have  - No, it's not a good idea.
你们俩不准再在一起  也不许再哭
Just stay away from each other. so much as a tear
也别朝对方看  就此打住
Or a glance in each other's direction, and it's over.
-我不明白  -我说话时别插嘴
- I don't understand-- - no, no, no. don't talk while I'm talking.
我就是想告诉你们这个
That's what I was...
现在给我出去
Now just get out.
走啊
Go.
分开走
Not together.
感觉好极了
Oh, that felt good.
你呼我  贝利医生
You paged me, Dr. Bailey?
对
Oh, yes.
你的脸部移植术完成了  对吧
you're finished with your part of the face transplant, right?
对  但我已经把时间安排用来
Yes, but I cleared my schedule
观摩斯隆和杨医生的手术
To watch Sloan and Dr. yang do their surgeries.
所以不管你要我干什么
So whatever it is you need,
我希望不要太久
I hope it's not too time consuming.
那取决于你开车和说话有多快了
That all depends on how fast you can drive and talk.
不好意思  什么
Uh, I'm sorry.
我要你开车去森林
I need you to drive out to the woods
说服德里克·谢博德回来
And talk derek shepherd into coming back here.
你应该也会碰到凯丽·托瑞斯
And I believe you also might run into callie torres,
她可能车胎爆了  或者鞋跟断了
With a flat tire or a broken heel
也可能是遇到挥着斧头的连环杀手了
Or an... ax-wielding serial killer.
-你说真的  -我让托瑞斯去找谢博德
- You're serious? - see, I sent torres after shepherd,
她神奇般消失了
And she's fallen off the grid.
给她打电话也转接到了语音信箱
Her phone goes straight to voice mail.
我不是一个疑神疑鬼的人
Okay, I... I'm normally not a panicky person,
但我爱看日间电视节目
But I'm a fan of daytime television,
所以会这样胡思乱想
And, you know, the mind creates these scenarios--
不说这个了
Uh, never mind.
我要你去找托瑞斯和谢博德
I need you to go get torres and shepherd
把他们带回来
And bring them back here
而且要在主任发现你们不见前
Before the chief notices that any of you are gone.
谢博德这一周都不在
Shepherd's been gone all week.
-我相信主任不会发现  -亨特
- I'm sure the chief wouldn't notice-- - Hunt!
你都从战场上活了回来
You survived a war. mm-hmm.
你能搞的定
You can do this.
我知道  我只是我不想做
I know I can do this. I'm saying I don't want to.
人们从来不会对你说不  对吧
People don't really say no to you, do they?
我求他们的时候就不会
Not when I say please.
我正在求你呢
I'm saying please.
手术室准备好了  移植专员马上就来
O.R.'s set. transport's on its way.
-准备好了吗  -我等这一刻等了12年了
- You ready? - I've been ready for 12 years.
你说你有些朋友
Y-you said you had some friends
-他们会来照顾你  -对  手术后来
- That were coming to take care of you? - yeah, after my surgery.
他们已经来了
They're coming now.
惊喜吧
Surprise!
我是仙妮亚
Hi, it's me, Shayna.
你看我捧的万带兰就能猜出来了吧
You can probably tell from my vanda rothschildiana.
希望你不会气我们提前到来
Uh, I hope you're not mad that we came early.
我们觉得应该全程陪着你
We thought we should be here through it all,
-让你感受到  -出去
- Make sure you knew-- - get out.
让他们出去  我不认识他们
Get them out. they're strangers.
我不想在这里看见他们
I don't want them in here.
戴夫  我们不是陌生人啊
Well, we're hardly strangers, Dave.
这么多年来我们每晚都聊天
We chat every night, all night for years.
-我们  -出去
- We--we flew in s-- -get out!
我们从没见过  你并不认识我
We've never met. you don't know me.
你根本不了解我  出去
You don't know anything about me. get out.
让他们出去  出去  出去
Get--get them out! get out! get out!
出去
Get out!
你收到我的传呼了吗
Hey, did you get my page?
帮你约好了  15分钟后开始
You got the appointment. it's in, like, 15 minutes.
我真是太厉害了
God, how amazing am i?
通常要花上好几周才能预约到
It usually takes weeks to get in there.
你看过研究报告了吗
Uh, did you take a look at the research?
你真要现在说  我就不能安静地吃个饭
seriously? can I just eat?
对不起  不能  你没时间了
No. I'm sorry. you don't have time.
什么没时间了
Time for what?
没啥  是一个要灌肠的
To do, uh, there's, uh, an enema.
伊兹要灌肠的
Uh, Izzie's enema.
对啊  我今天本来应该灌肠的
Yes, I was supposed to get an enema today,
但是我觉得还可以再等等
But I decided it can wait.
吃饭时时候咱能不说这个吗
How about we talk about something else?
不行  我们一定要说
N-no. we need to talk about it.
你一直抱怨便秘
You've been complaining about being really backed up,
现在我给你安排了个预约
And I got you an appointment.
哥们  你都要灌肠这么惨了
Dude, if you need an enema that bad,
那你不该把这些薯条全都吃了
maybe you shouldn't have all these fries.
你真给她安排了一个灌肠的预约
You really booked her an appointment for an enema?
你不能一边说自己便秘
You can't just say that you're all backed up
一边又坐着不动
and just sit there, Izzie.
伊兹如果下了决心去灌肠
If you make the decision to get an enema,
那就别犹豫了  去灌肠吧
then you should get an enema.
我看你才是便秘了
I think maybe you're the one that's backed up.
主刀手术紧张症吗
Solo surgery panic?
我保证我一定协助你
Tell you what--I'll scrub in with you.
要是你坚持不下来  我就接手
If you can't handle it, I'll take over.
我  我不是那个意思
I don't--i'm--no. okay.
我的意思是
You know, I'm just saying,
灌肠可是严肃的事情
Enemas can be a serious business.
伊兹猜谜时间结束  交代灌肠代表啥
Okay. Izzie, "enema" is code for what?
我的灌肠我喜欢
My enema, my business.
只要十五分钟哦
Uh, 15 minutes.
今天真是诡异的一天
This is a really strange day.
那时是我当住院医生的第二年
I was a second-year resident.
有一次来了很多车祸伤者
M.v.c. rolls in.
父母坐在前排  三个孩子坐在后排
Parents were in the front seat, three kids in the back.
孩子没事
Kids were okay.
父母受到了轻微撞伤  但是无大痒
Mom and dad were a little banged up, but nothing terrible.
他们在急救室里还有说有笑的
They were talking and laughing in the E.R.
可实际那对父母受了严重的内伤
Turns out both parents had massive internal injuries.
我抢救了他们整整一个晚上
I operated on them both that night--hours.
却两个都没保住
Lost 'em both.
如果我的速度要是能再快点
You know, if I had moved faster,
如果我赶紧送他们做CT
if I had rushed them to c.t.,
如果我一开始就确诊他们伤的很重
if I had known how bad off they were sooner,
可是我都没做到
But I didn't.
那个最大的孩子才九岁
The oldest kid was 9.
当我通知他们的父亲已经去世了
When I came out to tell 'em about their dad,
他还安慰三岁和五岁的弟妹
he was trying to console the 3 year old
说要等着妈妈平安回来
and the 5 year old about their mother.
那情景永远都留在我记忆中
I'll never get that image out of my head--this--
九岁的他努力去抱住年幼的弟妹
This 9-year-old boy trying to hold these 2 little ones,
他的手臂还那么孱弱
And his arms-- just not big enough.
第二天我是失魂落魄回的家
I don't know how I came back the next day.
我想这是我心里永远的伤痛了
I think part of me never did.
我真奇怪你怎么不说伊拉克的事
I'm surprised you didn't talk about Iraq.
我不想提伊拉克的事情
I don't talk about Iraq.
我的想法是
At I'm-- what my point was--
自从
I kept...
我回来后
You know, I... I went back.
我重新振作
I showed up. I...
我重新振作去工作
I showed up for work, you know?
也许你的内心已经枯萎了
Or you go dead inside.
你却未曾感知你内心的枯萎
You go dead inside because if you actually felt it?
若你有所感  你不可能从伊拉克回来
If you let yourself feel that? No way you're going back.
不可能
No way.
你失约了吗
You blew it off?
克里斯蒂娜  拜托你了
Cristina, please.
我用尽了在医院的人脉
I called every favor I had in this hospital
费劲了心机
And then some.
斯汪特是美国顶尖的肿瘤学家
Swender's the best surgical oncologist In this state.
-你为什么不去  -为什么你那么在乎
- Why didn't you go?  - why do you care so much?
你是怎么了  我为你废尽了心血
Oh, why don't you? I'm working really hard on this.
克里斯蒂娜至少你可以说
So the least you can do is
管理呼吸机的家伙可以帮你接电话
they were calling the guy blowhole, cristina.
可我呢  不光是那些实习生还有阿历克斯
Not just the interns-- Alex.
我做手术的时候他们给我打电话怎么办
What are they gonna call me when I'm the patient,
给大脑订一份瑞士奶酪吗
Swiss cheese for brains?
既尴尬又冗长
No. That's awkward and long.
管呼吸机的哥们真可悲
Blowhole's pithy.
我可不想坐医院的俎上之肉
I'm not gonna be a piece of meat in this hospital
等我开刀的时候你们还在工作着
While you all fight over who gets to slice me up
而且你们还面带微笑
and then laugh while you do it.
事情不是那样的
Okay, this right here--
是这样
This, um, is
你现在是感情用事
A-an emotional thing you're having--
所以你要告诉梅瑞狄斯和乔治
Which is why you should tell Meredith or George or--
我谁都不说  你就别费心思了
I'm not telling anybody, so just drop it.
不行  这件事你要听我的
No. y-you're not dumping this on me.
你可是在我知情的情形下慢慢死去
You're not dying in my arms.
你要不说我就说了
So either you tell them, or I will.
连做不做手术我都不确定  克里斯蒂娜
No, I don't even know if I want treatment, cristina.
你肯定需要手术
I know too much.
我知道做这个手术有多危险
I know how violent surgery can be.
他们要对我的大脑做手术
They're gonna cut into my brain.
他们要把我的肚子切开
They're gonna slice open my abdomen
然后把我的器官拽出来  我不想那样
And pull my organs out, and for what?
手术总是有失败的可能
Surgery fails all the time.
德瑞克·谢博德现在神经兮兮的
Derek shepherd is in the freakin' woods right now
正是因为手术失败
Because we fail all the time.
即使一切进行顺利
And even if they do everything right,
我只有5%的机会可能活下来  5%啊
I have a 5% chance of survival 5%
我自己跳进地狱得了
Why would I put myself through hell,
或者输点毒药 要么干脆辐射我的大脑
Run poison through my veins, irradiate my brain,
那样我看还死的利落
If it's not gonna work anyway?
那你告诉我干什么
Why did you tell me, then?
反正你也不想我帮你
If you don't want my help,
你什么都不想做
And you're not gonna do anything about it,
那干嘛告诉我
Why did you tell me?
赶紧把嘴巴闭上
Just keep your mouth shut
然后把我告诉你的全忘记
And forget I ever told you anything.
伊兹  你
Izzie. Oh.
戴夫  你要把他们叫回来
You need to call 'em back, Dave.
你是我的外科医生  对吧
You're my surgeon, right?
你不是我的心理医生
You're not my shrink.
你为什么不去做你的工作
So why don't you just do your job?
反正我也做不了我的工作
Because I can't do my job anymore.
花了三年才找到合适的候选人
It took us three years to find the right candidate,
你也算是合适的候选人了
And part of you being the right candidate
手术前需要有一个协助程序的
Is having a support system post-op.
你不能独自做这个手术
You cannot do this alone.
我们的职业准则是不允许
The ethics board will not allow me
让你独自面对手术
To let you do it alone.
你需要你的朋友
You need your friends.
你看见那兰花了吗
You see that orchid?
它很难看
It's--it's ugly.
对于一个不认识兰花的人来说
To anyone who doesn't know orchids,
它又黑又干  丑的要命
It's dark and droopy and it's ugly...
除非理解它
Unless you know it,
除非知道它是经历了怎样的艰辛
Unless you understand how it adapted
如今才能幸存下来
What it's lived through,
它要多坚强才能活下去
And how strong it had to be to survive.
那朵兰花的照片
A photo of that orchid,
是我朋友看过的我唯一的照片
That's the only picture my friends have seen of me.
我希望那是他们心中我的样子
And that's how I wanted them to picture me
直到我有了新脸
Until I had my new face.
人们都不敢直视我
People look away from me.
孩子看见我会哭
Kids cry and...
大人们闪躲我
Adults cringe.
他们都不直视我
They look away.
我不想要什么朋友
I didn't want my friends...
我  我不要他们
I d... I didn't want them
我不想别人看到我然后转开脸
To ever have any reason to look away.
他们并没有转开脸
They didn't look away.
你的那些朋友们
Your friends,
他们中没有人恐惧
They didn't cringe, not one of them.
他们中没人转开脸  是你把脸转开了
They didn't look away. You looked away.
你不信任他们  你转开了脸
You didn't trust them. you looked away from them.
让我们打个电话  他们马上就会回来
Look, let us call them. they flew all the way here.
让我们打电话好吗  现在还不晚
Just let us call them back. It's not too late.
戴夫  如果你还想手术
If you want this surgery, dave,
你要给他们一个机会
You gotta give 'em a chance.
主任
Oh, uh, chief?
贝利医生
Dr. Bailey.
最近心情如何
Ooh. how's your mood?
焦急并渴望着
Eager. Anxious.
我对斯隆的手术很期待啊
Uh, I'm excited about Sloan's face transplant.
我有点担心德瑞克·谢博德
I'm a little concerned about Derek shepherd,
-但是你瞧看  我  -我看着像心理医生吗
- But, you know, all in all  - Do I look like a therapist?
你先和我说话的
You asked.
我派出的亨特和托雷斯全都战败了
I've lost Hunt and Torres.
本来让他们去见谢博德
See, I-I sent them to get Shepherd,
但是他们到现在音信全无
And I never heard from them again.
我也只是想尽力帮帮谢博德
See, I was trying to solve the Shepherd situation
为您分忧
For you, sir,
但是貌似情况比之前糟糕了三倍
But it appears I've somehow made it three times worse.
但我保证向您报告我下一步的决定
So I'm telling you, and my next move, I believe,
我的决定就是报警
Is that I'm gonna call the police,
我有些怀疑他们已经横尸街头了
Because I'm half convinced they're all dead...
独臂男人在他们身上吐了口水
On a spit with a one-armed man
把他们变成了痰盂
Turning 'em into shish kebabs.
主任  基本上我就想到这些了
Sir, it's my mind, it just goes there.
别把自己逼的太急  这决定很难做的
Don't beat yourself up. It's a hard decision.
你和皮亚斯在一起一年了
Yeah, you've been with pierce for the whole year.
所以就跟着感觉走
Just listen to your heart.
别想的太多太复杂
Stop thinking so hard. exactly.
为什么他们还不开始
Why are they starting late?
他们装器官的容器有点问题
There was a problem with the recipient.
他们时间不多了
They've only got a few hours left
否则那张脸就不能移植了
For that face to still be viable.
快别说了  斯隆都快疯了
Oh, shoot. Sloan must be freaking out, right?
第三者你说什么呢
Home wrecker. what did you just say?
什么  你刚才说什么了
What? what did he just say?
-嘿  哥们  -你们两个都给我出去  你过来
- Guys, guys!  - Hey! you two, get out. you, come with me.
过来  就是你
Come on. hey, buddy.
你要说说心里话啊  说说吧
You need to start talking.You need to start talking now.
我不能说史蒂夫的事情
I really can't. Talk to Steve.
哥们你一定要说点什么啊
Ry-guy, you gotta start talking, dude... mnh-mnh.
因为他们随时可能开始
Because any second, they're gonna start
那个人脸移植手术  然后她的朋友
That face transplant surgery, and then her good friend
可是我最好的朋友哦
... my best friend.
马上就要做她的第一次主刀手术了
Is gonna have her very first solo surgery,
然后你瞧
And so...
我们目前可没啥耐心
We have very little patience right now.
-真的不关我的事情啊  -省省吧
- Look, it's not my place  - okay.
你必须给我说清来龙去脉
You are gonna tell me everything that's going on,
否则  每一次只要我有了直肠检查的
Or else every time I have a rectal exam
或者严重感染的溃疡
or an infected abscess,
就由你打头阵  注意我说的是每一次
It's gonna have your name on it. every time.
梅根是和皮亚斯在一起的
Megan was with Pierce,
但后来他们分了手
But they broke up for a little bit.
他们分手后  她和史蒂夫睡在了一起
While they were broken up, she slept with Steve,
后来她又和皮亚斯和好了
And then she got back together with Pierce.
但是史蒂夫又给她发了邮件
But Steve Sent her an e-mail
说了他们睡觉的事情
about how they slept together,
而且不光是给她一个人发的
And instead of just e-mailing her,
他把邮件群发  大家全都看见了
He hit "reply all," went to a whole bunch of people,
其中也包括皮亚斯
One of 'em was Pierce.
现在史蒂夫示爱了  皮亚斯想宰了他
And now Steve says he loves her. Pierce wants to kill him.
梅根都神经了  因为
Megan's, like, really freaking out, right? Because...
等等  倒带一下  刚说有人发了邮件
Okay, wait, so a while back, someone sent
纠正下是短信息
This text message, right?
事先声明  我没收到  我也没有看
And, like, I didn't get it. I didn't get to see it.
那短信只给几个人发了
It just came to certain people's phones, you know...
为什么他们回来了
Why would they come back?
我很残忍  很可怕
I was cruel. I was hateful.
你是害怕而已  他们吓到你了
You were scared. they surprised you.
你被吓到了  并且你没料到
You were in shock, and it wasn't what you were expecting.
-你只是  你只是  -我很可怕
You were... you were just-- I was awful.
你只是受了惊吓
You were scared.
你想去保护他们
And you were trying to protect them.
如果他们是你的朋友  他们就能理解
If they're your friends, they'll understand.
我不想你看到它
I didn't want you to see it.
这丑东西  不是我
This--this ugliness, it isn't me.
我不想你们看到它
I-i didn't want you to see it.
就在这
This right here...
就像兰花月见草
It looks just like the coryanthes speciosa.
你们都看到了吗
You guys see that?
她是对的
She's right.
颜色都一样
The coloring's just the same.
如果没做手术
If the surgery doesn't take,
如果拒绝了别人的面部捐献  我会更丑
If--if I reject the donor face, I'll be uglier.
甚至会比现在更难看
I'll--i'll be even uglier than I am right now.
请不要说我亲爱的朋友难看
Please don't call my dear friend ugly.
你是幸存者
You're a survivor.
并且都写在你脸上了
And it's written all over your face.
到底怎么了  这样不行
What the hell is this? oh, this is not okay.
我要经营医院
I have a hospital to run.
德瑞克  你究竟怎么了
And, derek, what the hell's the matter with you, man?
我们都在这  我们说了这个
We've all been there. we said that.
-我们都有过严重的损失  -他知道
We've all had tough losses. he knows that.
第二天照常上班  然后去救
We show up the next day, and we try and save
-下一条命  -没错  我们提了这个
The next life. yeah, we covered that, too.
好  那这算什么
Okay, what about this?
面对死亡我们无能为力
Nothing we do can stop death.
也许偶尔可以控制它
We can hold it at bay now and then,
但每个人都会死
But everyone dies.
并且也不是我们的错
And that's not on us.
我给一个孕妇做了简单的手术
I took a pregnant woman in for a simple surgery
我搞砸了
And I botched it.
这是我的错  我活该受良心谴责
That is on me. I should feel badly about that.
那么你呢
And you?
我不在你就会觉得很糟糕
You should feel badly that while I was out here,
你把梅丽狄斯叫到这来期待我的求婚
You sent meredith out here expecting a ring.
你为什么要这样做
Why would you do that?
以上帝的名义你为什么要这样做
Why in god's name would you do that?
我想要帮忙的
I... I was trying to help.
她不愿意来
She didn't want to come.
我是说  她想让你静一静
I mean, she wanted to leave you out here alone.
我想帮忙的  德里克
I... I was trying to help, derek.
你只是想帮你自己  不是我
You were trying to help yourself, not me.
你自己
Yourself.
我弄响了树林里铃
I hit the ring in the woods.
树林里的
In the woods.
你毁了我
You destroyed me.
你将做一个面部粘合
You'll place the facial graft.
我会把动脉和神经粘合起来
I'll be connecting the vessels and nerves.
显微镜准备
Get the microscope ready.
好了  时间到了
Okay, people, it's time.
你有给过别人新面孔吗
You ever put a new face on someone?
真的吗
Really?
右边我来  你做左边
I'll take the right side, you take the left.
很轻的
Very gently.
就是它了
That's it.
花点时间  他哪也去不了
Take your time. he's not going anywhere.
没问题
Okay.
看看他左边嘴
Watch the left corner of his mouth.
你只是离开中心一点而已
You're off center just a bit.
接下来
There we go.
眼睛周围要小心
Careful around the eyes.
好  很好  格蕾医生
Good. very good, Dr. Grey.
-出去  -不
- Get out.- no.
-理查德  -不
- Richard!- no!
出来
Get out!
看  我手上有很多条人命
Look, I've destroyed lives before,
事实上很多  你不是其中之一
Several in fact, and yours is not one of them.
我调派你爱的女人来这里帮你
I sent the woman you love out here to help you.
我还调派爱你的女人来这里帮你
I sent the woman who loves you out here
让你重返你的生活
To bring you back to your life.
若你和她一起把这事情搞砸了  你负全责
If you ruined it with her, that's on you.
我不接受
I don't accept it.
你害怕了  你醉了  不知道对的方向
You're scared. you're drunk.you don't know which way is up.
你朝你最好的朋友扔酒瓶子
You threw a punch at your best friend,
你朝梅丽狄斯扔  现在又想赶我走
You threw a ring at Meredith,now you want to throw me out.
我不接受  因为我比你年纪大
I'm not accepting it, because I'm older than you,
走过的桥比你走过的路还多
And I've been where you are.
你醉了很多天  而我醉了很多年
You been drunk for a few days. I was drunk for years.
我知道你决定从自己挖的洞里出来时
And I know you're gonna need at least one friend
至少需要有个朋友拉你一把
When you decide to come out of that hole you're digging.
我希望你快点出来
I hope you come out of it soon.
所以我在你身旁等你叫我拉你
I'll be here when you do.
我想她不会回来了
I don't think I can get her back.
你给她打电话了吗
Did you call her?
我要说什么
What am I gonna say?
我有婚外情很多年了
I had an affair for years.
当阿戴尔发现  不知怎么她
And when Adele found out, somehow she...
她把我带回来
She took me back.
而你不管发生什么
You can make your way back...
都能自己回来
From anything.
这是你实习期间中的一年
This is year one of your residency.
你们轮流值班
You turn on each other now,
你不想这么过日子
You're not gonna make it.
好  接下来
Okay, here's what's gonna happen--
你们所有人都给我去反省
All of you are going to go find the sense
万能的主给了你们哪些恩赐
That the good lord gave you
永远不准再在医院的四墙之内
And never behave like this within the four walls
出现这样的举止
Of this hospital ever again.
你们是医生
You are doctors.
皮尔斯  拿个冰袋
Pierce, get an ice pack
把它放在那只恶心的淤青一团的眼睛上
And put it on that oozing, disgusting mess of an eye.
史蒂夫  去那坑里
And, Steve, go to the pit
弄只不卫生的
And get that unsanitary
照过X光缝过线的血淋淋的手来缝合一下
Bloody hand x-rayed and stitched.
还有梅根  你应该去妇产科
And, Megan, you should go to o.b.
因为  没错  你怀孕了
Because, yes, you are pregnant.
这很贝利啊
That was very Bailey.
你准备好了吗  杨医生
You ready, Dr. Yang?
等等  不好意思
Wait. I'm sorry.
在你下刀之前我要你给我样东西
I need one thing from you before I go under.
现在我没有过分的要求
Now I haven't asked for much.
你没有回答我的问题
You haven't answered my questions,
我知道你很忙
And I understand that you're busy,
但我很害怕  我不想死
But I'm scared. I don't want to die.
明年我想和朋友去俄罗斯看看
I want to go on a tour of Russia with my friends next year.
我对你来说也许只是个奇怪的老女人
I may just be a batty old lady to you,
这也许是个愚蠢的小程序
And this may be a silly little procedure,
不过我要你告诉我一切会好起来的
But I need you to tell me that it's gonna be okay.
毕竟你是我的医生
You're my surgeon, after all.
这不是愚蠢的程序  对我而言  萨利女士
This isn't a silly procedure, to me, ms. Sully.
我会帮你度过难关的
And I will get you through this.
谢谢
Thank you.
我现在准备好了
I'm ready now.
伊兹有第四期脑肿瘤
Izzie has stage iv metastatic melanoma
已经扩散到她脑子  肝  还有皮肤
That has spread to her brain, liver and skin.
她可能只有没几个月可活了
She may only have months to live,
但她拒绝治疗
And she's resisting treatment.
她需要帮助
She needs help.
手术刀
Scalpel.
不  不  别开口  戴夫
No, no, don't try to talk, Dave.
这样有弊无利  你做的很好
It'll only hurt. you did great.
他能看看他的新形象吗
Can he see his new face?
我想他很想看了  不过还太早
I think he'd really like to see it. it's still early.
现在是又肿又伤
It's very swollen and bruised.
组织需要时间去恢复
The tissue needs time to settle.
不过  我给你偷偷看一下
But yeah. I'll give you a sneak peek.
有时候我们会失败  不过不是一直那样
Sometimes we fail, but that's not always the case.
我知道  通风孔有新脸蛋了
I know. blowhole has a new face.
你知道  为了让他度过那段日子
You know, and what people call him
大家对他说了什么吗
To get through the day is--
克里斯蒂娜  我知道
Cristina, I know.
我告诉艾力克斯了
I told Alex
还有贝利
And Bailey.
他们告诉了梅丽狄斯和乔治
And they're telling Meredith and George.
克里斯蒂娜
Cristina--
不  我做不到
No, I couldn't do my job.
我知道你是来向我寻求帮助的
I think you came to me for help,
那也是我所做的
And that's what I did.
因为有时候我们会赢  伊兹
Because sometimes we win, Izzie.
我希望你挑战
And I want you to fight
好吗
Okay?
你知道  不管为了什么
You know, for whatever that's worth,
我想你去挑战
I want you to fight.
谢谢
Thank you.
格蕾医生吗
Dr. Grey?
他们认为你占我便宜
They think that you're taking advantage of me,
他们认为我在利用你
And they think that I'm using you.
不过他们不了解我们
But they don't know us.
他们认为我们很丑陋
They think that we're ugly,
不过我知道我们很美
But I know that we're beautiful.
我们可以接受一个敌对的环境
And we can adapt to a hostile environment.
谢谢你来
Thanks for coming.
谢谢你叫我
Thanks for calling.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道
I know.
如果我不是医生了你还爱我吗
Would you still love me if I wasn't a surgeon?
不
No.
不  因为伊兹
No, because Izzie...
皮肤癌扩散到她脑子了
Has skin cancer that spread to her brain.
你是世界上仅有的20个
And you're one of about 20 people in the world
能救她的人
Who can save her.
我不知道自己是否会尊敬
And I don't know if I could respect somebody
放弃天赐良机重新走出困境的人
Who could walk away from a gift like that.
所以请继续作医生
So please don't.
这里是她的扫描
Here are her scans.
很糟糕
It's pretty bad.
用药期间
Practicing medicine
不宜交友
Doesn't lend itself well to making friends...
也许是因为  生命和死亡
Maybe because life and mortality...
都在我们脸上写着
Are in our faces all the time...
也许因为每天都更接近死亡
Maybe because in staring down death every day...
我们无奈而知  生命的
We're forced to know that life...
每一秒钟
Every minute...
都是借来的
Is borrowed time...
每一个我们心头牵挂的人
And each person we let ourselves care about...
接二连三的在人生中迷失自我
Is just one more loss somewhere down the line.
因此...
For this reason...
我知道有的医生根本不会
I know some doctors who just don't bother
为交友而扰
Making friends at all.
但我们会
But the rest of us...
我们把帮助他们纠正方向视为自己的责任
We make it our job to move that line...
去让每一个失去生命的可能
To push each loss...
尽量的远离我们
As far away as we can.